_[Saiga NAK](https://saiganak.com/)_

 English 

* [English](https://saiganak.com/en/privacy/ "English (en)")
* [日本語](https://saiganak.com/ja/privacy/ "日本語 (ja)")
* [繁體中文](https://saiganak.com/zh/privacy/ "繁體中文 (zh)")

* * *

* * *

* * *

 Search

[Top](https://saiganak.com/) >  Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy
==============

### Art.1 Definition of Personal Information

The term "personal information" as used in this Site's Privacy Policy shall mean information about a living individual which can identify the specific individual by name, addresses, phone numbers, and email addresses or other description contained in such information (including such information as will allow easy reference to other information and will thereby enable the identification of the specific individual). We define "personal information" based on Japanese Personal Information Protection law.

### Art.2 Personal Information We Collect

Saiga NAK ("Site") collects and uses the personal information our Users provide for registration, viewing, and using the Site. We collect and use them legally and fairly, and we do not collect the Users' personal information by any unlawful means.

### Art.3 Disclosure of Personal Information to Third Parties

To be based on the Japanese Personal Information Protection law, we will not sell, share, or otherwise distribute your personal information to third parties except under the following circumstances.

1. When the disclosure of the personal information is lawfully accepted.
2. When the disclosure of the personal information is lawfully required.
3. When the personal information is required for protecting individuals' lives, bodies, or properties but not able to obtain the person's consent.
4. When the disclosure of the personal information is required by public institutions such as the police, the public prosecutors office, the courts, and the consumer information center.

### Art.4 Disclaimer

This Site is not responsible for acquisition of any personal information from a third party under the following circumstances.

1. When a User leaks the personal information to a third party through our services or any other ways.
2. When a User certificates acquisition of personal information from a third party.
3. When a User acquires any personal information from our linked sites.

### Art.5 Modification of the Purpose of Use

The Privacy Policy of this site may be modified and made changes at anytime without notice. This Privacy Policy was last modified on the date indicated above and is effective immediately. Your continued use of this Site after any changes to these Policies are posted will be considered acceptance of those changes.

### Art.6 Use of third-party companies' services and their privacy policies

This site uses cookies and other technologies for website access analysis or to provide optimal advertising. cookies can identify a user's browser, but cannot identify individual users.  
Cookies can be disabled to refuse collection, so please check your browser settings.  
This site uses the following services

* Microsoft Clarity  
* Google Analytics  
* Google AdSense  
* Yandex.Metrica  
* User Local  
* ACCESSTRADE  
* Affiliates.One  
* Involve Asia  
* ChineseAN  
* OneSignal  
* Amazon Japan  
    [https://www.amazon.co.jp/gp/help/customer/display.html?nodeId=201909010](https://www.amazon.co.jp/gp/help/customer/display.html?nodeId=201909010)
* LinkShare  
* ValueCommerce  
* JANet  
* adstir  
* i-mobile  
* ID5  

To review the privacy policy of a third-party company's service, please refer to the URL of the privacy policy of each service.

[Verified Site

Trusted by

See Report](https://www.mywot.com/scorecard/saiganak.com?wot_badge=2_white)

All the issues and problems will be resolved pursuant to our Japanese Privacy Policy.

###  New entry

* [_![[ACGHK 2024]  Cosplayers from Hong Kong Biggest Anime Event ACGHK  Part2](https://i0.wp.com/saiganak.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/acghk2024-cosplayer-part2-00-150x150.jpg "[ACGHK 2024]  Cosplayers from Hong Kong Biggest Anime Event ACGHK  Part2")_
    
    **\[ACGHK 2024\] Cosplayers from Hong Kong Biggest Anime Event ACGHK Part2**2024.08.17(Sat)](https://saiganak.com/event/acghk2024-cosplayer-part2/ "[ACGHK 2024]  Cosplayers from Hong Kong Biggest Anime Event ACGHK  Part2")
* [__
    
    **Show Girl Special Feature at ACGHK 2024 – Hong Kong’s Biggest Anime Festival!**2024.08.01(Thu)](https://saiganak.com/event/acghk2024-promotional-model/ "Show Girl Special Feature at ACGHK 2024 – Hong Kong’s Biggest Anime Festival!")
* [_![[EVO 2024] Photo Report from Las Vegas!](https://i0.wp.com/saiganak.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/evo-2024-booth-photo-report-00-150x150.jpg "[EVO 2024] Photo Report from Las Vegas!")_
    
    **\[EVO 2024\] Photo Report from Las Vegas!**2024.07.21(Sun)](https://saiganak.com/event/evo-2024-booth-photo-report/ "[EVO 2024] Photo Report from Las Vegas!")
* [__
    
    **The esports exclusive brand Victrix has launched an official X account in Japan!**2024.07.11(Thu)](https://saiganak.com/news/victorix-opens-official-japan-x/ "The esports exclusive brand Victrix has launched an official X account in Japan!")
* [__
    
    **GiGO Vietnam Launches on June 28, Expanding Amusement Centers into Southeast As…**2024.07.04(Thu)](https://saiganak.com/news/gendagigo-vietnam/ "GiGO Vietnam Launches on June 28, Expanding Amusement Centers into Southeast Asia")

### Pocket ranking

* No article

* [!")
    
    I Tried 'SURVIVOR'! Japan's Affordable Energy Drink Available for 100 Yen (0.68 USD)!](https://saiganak.com/review/survivor-energy-drink-testing/ "I Tried 'SURVIVOR'! Japan's Affordable Energy Drink Available for 100 Yen (0.68 USD)!")
* [
    
    Chainsaw Man × ZONe！Collaboration New "ZONe BLOOD" On Sale!](https://saiganak.com/product/chainsawman-collabo-zone-blood-release/ "Chainsaw Man × ZONe！Collaboration New ")
* [
    
    Haomaru's favorite sword "Meito FuguDoku"on sale!](https://saiganak.com/product/meitoh-fugudoku-preorder/ "Haomaru's favorite sword ")
* [
    
    Final Fantasy 35th Anniversary UNIQLO T-Shirts coming back in Late June!](https://saiganak.com/product/ff35th-anniversary-ut-additional-production/ "Final Fantasy 35th Anniversary UNIQLO T-Shirts coming back in Late June!")
* [
    
    New designs for DualSense and PS5 covers featuring FF XVI Available! Along with a bundle for PS5!](https://saiganak.com/product/ps5-ffxvi-limited-items-release/ "New designs for DualSense and PS5 covers featuring FF XVI Available! Along with a bundle for PS5!")

We have been strictly prohibited without permission . copyright of images, text , etc. that have been published in saiganak.com is attributable to saiganak.com or photographer - writer.

_saiganak.com_ **[esports media | Saiga NAK](https://saiganak.com/ "esports media | Saiga NAK")**
